http://recoveryspecialties.com/privacy.html#uopi

Privacy Statement
Your privacy is important to Recovery Specialties. This statement discloses the information practices for Recovery Specialties Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.
Personal Information
Use of Personal Information
- Fulfilling Your Request
- Marketing Use
Information Security and Quality
Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies
Online Advertising
Disclosures Required By Law
Personal Information
You can visit Recovery Specialties on the Internet without telling us who you are and
without providing any personal information about you or your company.
Recovery Specialties, LLC collects
no information whatsoever regarding your visits to this site. As we do not collect or maintain any of this
type of information, we can not sell, share, or otherwise disclose any information about your visits.
There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you.
You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to
provide us information, such as your name and address or e-mail id, to correspond with you, to register
for a conference or special event, or to provide you with a newsletter or other materials.
If such information is
provided, it will be provided solely at your discretion and via email, regular mail or telephone.
This information is never solicited by Recovery Specialties via a web portal nor is this
information maintained on this site.
If you indicate that you do not want us to use this information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you provide personal information about someone else, such as a spouse or work colleague, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.
Return to the Top
Use of Personal Information
The following paragraphs describe in more detail how Recovery Specialties may use your personal information and with whom we may share it.
Return to the Top
Fulfilling Your Request
If you request something from Recovery Specialties, for example, information regarding a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.
Return to the Top
Marketing Use
The information you provide to Recovery Specialties may also be used by Recovery Specialties for marketing purposes. Before we use it, however, we will offer you the opportunity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way.
Return to the Top
Information Security and Quality
We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality, privacy and integrity.
We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting or storing sensitive
client information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality.
Return to the Top
Supplementing Information
From time to time we may supplement information you provide us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information about businesses. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide a better service.
Return to the Top
Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies
The Recovery Specialties web site does not use Cookies, Web Beacons nor any other technology to acquire any personal information about your visit.
Return to the Top
Online Advertising
Certain companies help us deliver interactive on-line advertising such as banner ads. These companies may
collect and use information about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of
advertising that are most appealing to our customers. After it is collected the information is aggregated so it
is not identifiable to a specific individual. If, however, you would prefer that these companies not collect
such information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/ and follow the "opt-out" instructions.
Return to the Top
Disclosures Required By Law
Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.
Return to the Top
Privacy Technology
Technology will increasingly help give you more control over your personal information. It will also help organizations to manage their privacy practices and policies. As an information technology provider, Recovery Specialties actively supports the development of privacy technologies to help achieve these goals and to help create greater trust and confidence in the way personal information is handled.
Return to the Top
Links to non-Recovery Specialties Web Sites
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that the Recovery Specialties, LLC is not
responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our
site and to read the privacy statements of every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
The Recovery Specialties privacy statement applies solely to
Recovery Specialties,
LLC.
Return to the Top
Surveys and Contests
From time to time our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is
completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
Information requested may include demographic information such as name and shipping address, zip code, or age
level. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Return to the Top
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. All client information is
restricted in our offices, with no client information being assessable via this web site.
Return to the Top
Notification of Changes
This privacy statement was last updated on August 24, 2006. A notice will be posted on our Web site home page for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed in a material way.
Return to the Top
Privacy Questions and Access
If you have a question about this statement, you can send an email to the Recovery Specialties Web site coordinator. The address for this is email:info@recoveryspecialties.com. You can also contact us at this address if you have a question about Recovery Specialties' handling of your information.
Contact us:
info@recoveryspecialties.com
Recovery Specialties, LLC
Enterprise Storage Solutions,
Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery consulting for z/OS environments
This document was printed from http://recoveryspecialties.com/
